{
    "subject": "resource/Marion_Francis_Forst",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1910-09-03",
    "human_readable": "Marion Francis Forst was born on September 3, 1910.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9043571352958679,
            "question": "When was Marion Francis Forst born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.900663435459137,
            "question": "Who was born on September 3, 1910?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8271404504776001,
            "question": "What is the birthdate of Marion Francis Forst?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8068484663963318,
            "question": "What is Marion Francis Forst's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7244123816490173,
            "question": "What is the specific date of Marion Francis Forst's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6323432922363281,
            "question": "On which day did Marion Francis Forst celebrate their birthday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5491939187049866,
            "question": "In what year did Marion Francis Forst come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5144086480140686,
            "question": "When did Marion Francis Forst enter the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40363791584968567,
            "question": "Who celebrates a birthday on September 3rd?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36558958888053894,
            "question": "September 3rd holds significance for whom?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marion Francis Forst was born on September 3, 1910.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3997_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who celebrates a birthday on September 3rd?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3997_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Marion Francis Forst enter the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3997_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Marion Francis Forst come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3997_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3997_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3997_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3997_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3997_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3997_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3997_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3997_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3997_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3997_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3997_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe document states that Marion Francis Forst was born on September 3, 1910, which matches the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Marion Francis Forst was born on September 3, 1910, but the context information provided states that his birthdate was on September 27, 1910.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There are multiple individuals born on September 3, 1910, listed as having different occupations and nationalities.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}